<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo on Blog - Guel Bandeira</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/hugo/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo on Blog - Guel Bandeira</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2026 14:26:46 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/hugo/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to self-host Remark42 on Debian for a Hugo blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-setup-remark42-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-setup-remark42-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>This post documents the exact process that worked for me when self-hosting Remark42 behind a Cloudflare Tunnel on my Hugo blog. No theory, no dead ends, only the final, functional setup that I have found after hours of debugging errors and permissions.&#xA;1 - This is what we are going to set up:&#xA;Comments powered by Remark42 on your Hugo blog Cloudflare Tunnel running on a Debian server + Docker No public IP Access via HTTPS Setup Cloudflare Tunnel Setup with Cloudflare CLI (Recommended) If creating a tunnel through Docker didn&amp;rsquo;t work for you, you can do the following steps:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to add a favicon on a Hugo blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-add-favicon-on-hugo-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/how-to-add-favicon-on-hugo-blog/</guid>
      <description>Get your icon After choosing the icon you want to appear on your website, use CloudConvert to convert your favicon to .ico. You can also use any other website that converts images to .ico format, there are plenty of options available.&#xA;Select the extension of your favicon, choose ICO, and click Convert:&#xA;Add your favicon to Hugo Open your hugo.toml file and add the following lines:&#xA;[params] favicon = &amp;#34;/favicon.ico&amp;#34; Test to see if it works That’s it!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to create a free blog?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>What tool did I use? This blog runs at no cost, with no database and on a free host. To not lie to you, the only cost I had was the domain name, for $10, but I already had that domain for my portfolio, and you can host this blog without using your custom domain. For the blog itself this runs without any money from my pockets, and the tool I used is called Hugo, a Go framework designed to build static websites.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
